FROM ME TO YOU
It's Sanada and Sawako.
You see? I told you! Well,
let's give them all our support.
Ka... ze... haya?!
I've never faced this before...
...So I have no clue... if this is
the real deal... or if I'm wrong.
But if I listen to my
feelings... I hear my heart scream...
"I hope this feeling is love.
I wish for this to be love."
And it rings out... loud... and
clear... over everything else.
LOVE
Wha? ... But why?
Why?!
Guess that's that.
- What? Kurumi started all those rumors?
- Yeah, probably.
That little rat!
Hey, stop a sec.
Th... That's not fair, Yano-chin! You knew
this entire time? So why did you keep it
from me?
Well, that's because...
Wait, why the heck would she do that? It
makes no sense. If anything, she should be
thanking me, so what's the deal with
her harassing me like this instead?!
Well, that's because...
I wonder...
What? Tell me. Just in case.
Okay, well, its kinda
just a gut feeling but...
Y'know how my social awareness tends to
be pretty sharp sometimes? No one else may
have noticed, but I've had a pretty
strong inkling about it for a while now...
I think that girl probably has a
massive crush on Ryu that she's hiding.
She must've misunderstood our
relationship! I mean, you obviously know
this, but Ryu and I are
basically siblings, so...
Kurumiiii Kurumi, huh...
Let's see... That'd make her... Yikes. Just
imagining her as a sister in law makes me
- bleh.
- S... seriously?! Wha-?
It's obvious to literally everyone
else that she's liked Kazehaya from the
beginning!
- Huh?! No way!
- Y- You really didn't
know at all, did you?
Sorry. I just couldn't help it.
It bothered me... too much.
My whole body... is shaking.
Kuronuma.
I was wondering if you... like Ryu?
Like?
Like... Like.
Like.
Like!
The person that I like... so much...
...That my heart could burst is... Kazehaya.
No, it's more than that... I love him.
Th- The feelings that I have about
Sanada,... well, they're not romantic at
all.
Yes, he was kind to
me, and he did save me...
But... but...
Those feelings are different.
It's 'cause... he's just a friend.
I was wrong?
Then I'm gonna take your word for it.
M'kay.
Aw man...
Please don't look at me.
- I'm super embarrassed right now.
- Uh...
Woah I just realized, that what I said
just now about Sanada was probably
extremely rude. Uh, but, um... Let's see... I
have a lot of respect for him as a person...
He's a good guy! S- so, um...
You're okay. Sorry, All good.
I mean... this is what
liking someone is, right?
Everything I feel towards the person in
front of me. All of it... is "that" kind of
love, isn't it?
Jeez...
I just wanted to help you
but... I'm making things worse.
Wha...?
And From now on... there might be certain
things or times when I can't help you. If
that happens, then I'm sorry.
I'm not... I'm not the great
guy you think I am, Kuronuma.
I'm reckless and selfish too.
So what?
Even if you are really
those things... it's okay.
I mean it. I don't
need you to be my savior.
Alright?
What do you think about the idea...
Of going out sometime?
Huh? Uh... to where?
I mean like... boyfriend and girlfriend.
H-h-how very g-g-grown up! Th-th-that's
what a-adults do! M-m-mature adults! Isn't
- that right?
- U- um... At least I think...
I can't even imagine it!
The dating world seems so distant from
mine. I-I don't know anything about it.
I bet... the idea of going out with
someone... has never crossed her mind.
... U Umm I lack the experience
required to give you an answer.
Let me think... If I were
Yano, how would I respond?
Well... That's fine.
Huh?
For now at least... it's fine.
I don't understand any of it!
Like I just said.
If she's had a thing for Kazehaya, then
why on earth would she help out other
- girls who like him?
- Like I'm trying to say, she wanted
- to keep him from getting a girlfriend.
- Huh?
Her goal from the start was to make
everyone join that stupid agreement. And
that's why she kept sending girls to you
who'd have absolutely no chance with him.
- Now you've completely lost me.
- That's fine. You don't
really need to understand.
Hey.
Ryu, Sadako told us that she
was looking for you earlier.
Yeah, I saw her. 'Guess
she left a message for me?
Wait, you mean like a note?
Well, I mean,' to be honest
I doubt it was really her.
Lemme see.
Th- This... This clearly
isn't Sadako's handwriting!
So did you find that
in your shoe locker, or?
Yeah, I did.
And when you met with
Sawako, did anyone else come?
Shota and... Uh, that one girl. The one
with the long wavy hair and the weird
name...
- Wait her?!
- Oh yeah?
- A- Again with that terrifying expression.
- I had a hunch before,
but now I'm very confident.
I may have no idea what's going on but,
I'm gonna go find that brat' right now.
Haaaaa! -Hold it!
Why-eee?! What are you stopping me
for?!] It isn't fair, Yano-chin. You kept
all this info to yourself!
Because I knew you were gonna run off
like that so I wanted to keep quiet until
- I was sure.
- Well, now that you are,
let's do something, okay?
Not quite yet. We still
need a little more evidence.
Like what?
Well, the kind of solid evidence that she
would never be able to deny. So yeah... I'll
crush her so bad we'll never
hear a peep out of her again.
S- Scary...
Why... Why aren't you coming back, Kazehaya?
Should I have followed and gotten in
between them instead? No, he'd think I was
overbearing and desperate.
But what if... What if they start dating
after this? Kazehaya, hurry up and come
back to me.
Ka...
Ka?
Get outta here!
It's her! That creepy kid from earlier...
W- What are you doing here?
- Cones! I figured I'd help put them away.
- Okay... then hurry and do that.
... Well, there was a little mix-up. One of
the other committee members has the key I
need, so I have to wait.
Huh? The key? Well, I have
one on me. No waiting needed.
Why won't you leave?
Um, well, that's, uh- because I...
Why don't you leave?!
Kazehaya's gonna come back!
W- Why's she fidgeting around like that?
Why is she always there wherever I
go? Why does she act cutesy with me?!
I- It all makes sense now!
Sorry, but... I'm not a
creep so I'm only into adults.
... Huh?
Though... I understand why you feel that
way. If I were a woman, I'd be in love
with myself too.
Buuut, sorry, you're still a decade
too young to consider. You understand?
Wha... What are you even...
Why am I being rejected by this
dude?!...And how did we even get here?!
It'd be best if you moved on and
settled for some brat your own age.
Wha...
Oh Whoops. I wasn't trying
to eavesdrop or anything.
' It's not-
Hey. It's cool. I'm not
gonna tell a soul, I swear.
- That's not what-
- Shota, you damn brat! I
- knew you were slacking off!
- Crap.
- Impeccable timing.
- Kaze--
I've got an extra
difficult job for you to do.
C'mon! Cut me some slack!
- You've got it wrong! Listen!]
- Right.
It's better you just forget about me.
Pin, you better not start running
your mouth about what just happened.
Who do you think you are,
telling me what I can and can't do?
N- Nooo!
- Those rumors?
- Mhm by the time we had noticed them,
it seemed they'd been going around for a
while, right?
So, we honestly aren't sure if she
was responsible for spreading it or not.
- Gotcha.
- Yeah Sorry we couldn't help more.
I'm kinda surprised no
one seems to remember.
I guess we'll have to
hit up Class A then.
I had the strawberry flavor!
- Seems like it.
- Was it good?
Yeah, I hear it helps when you're tired.
Then maybe I'll go out and
get one after school today.
It's Tomo and Ekko. All
right, let's try asking them.
Will do!
Seriously?!
Y- Yeah, we happened to hear
her spreading gossip around.
And you're certain... it was her?
She's the one who comes to see Kazehaya
sometimes... it's definitely the same
- person... Right?
- Mmhm.
Now that you mention it, that was first
time we heard those rumors about you two
and Sadako.
We honestly were really surprised that
little rumors like that could be so
- hurtful.
- Thanks for sharing! We appreciate it!
Yano-chin, with this--
Now We've got you in our
siiights, Ku '-ru- mi!
Uh-Oh! It's Yano-chin's evil witch face!
Stay behind me, okay guys? Things might
get dangerous!
Just you watch! I'll even make you cough
up the exact brand of skin toner you use!
What?? You have a
personal grudge too? Whoa!
Huh? Yano and Yoshida are gone.
Ah... Maybe they're at volleyball practice.
Guess what? "There's someone that I like."
If I told them that. I
wonder how they'd react?
I can't even imagine saying it! -A-all
I know is that even the idea of it is
e-embarrassing... -What's she doing?
- A victory dance?
- Oh no, my heart's starting
- to pound. Wh-What should I do?
- The twist?
But I'm so happy.
I don't have to keep it to myself either.
I can share these feelings. And it makes
me even happier.
I get to have this love for Kazehaya... and
I also get friends that I can process all
these new things with... ...I had no idea
how truly, truly happy this would make me.
There's someone I like.
The person I like it's Kazehaya.
The first person I tell... should be her.
Afterall... she was open with
me and told me her feelings.
...So I want to tell her mine as well.
Somewhere along the line... we
became close enough to talk about love...
Well, well, well... What's been
going on here, Care to enlighten us?
It's strange Since you never spread
any of those rumors about us, right?
What're you talking about?
Don't play dumb with us. I promise you it
isn't gonna work. We've already gathered
witness accounts from
the girls in Class A.
Oh, wow! A Samurai drama!
Can you just be cool?
Yeah whatever even if I did spread some
gossip, so did most of the others girls,
so there's no proof I was
the source of the rumors.
What the?! You still tryin' to say this
smooth, shiny skin hasn't done anything
wrong?
You think I can't tell the difference
between someone with an amazing skincare
routine and someone who
doesn't put any effort in? Huh?
Mission De railed.
Drop the act already! We went around and
asked every damn student in this school,
to prove that you're guilty!
H- How could Yano-chin tell such a big
fat lie?! Also, That girl is a piece of
work.
- Hey! Your turn!
- Now listen here!
The jig is up, girly! We've already
thoroughly examined your handwriting. It
was compared to the evidence on my right.
- And your point is?
- That's why... w-well...
Uh, B- Because this is your handwriting!
You know liars go to hell, don'tchaaa? ...
Kay, don't worry about it You've done
enough here. By the way Compared to
earlier, you seem different.
Tell me, did everything end
up going according to plan?
Huh?
Ayane! Chizu! Kurumi!
Sawako.
Oh! This is unexpected! All three of you
are here! Did you all make friends with
- each other?
- No, we were chewing her out.
Say wha-?
The one who spread those rumors from
the bathroom incident... was Kurumi.
Sawako... the person responsible
for all that pain you went through...
It was all her.
I want to tell her... the
answer that I finally found.
Next time: "Kurumi"